ELINAM TRENDS
--------------------------------------------------------------


ABOUT OUR SERVICE
--------------------------------------------------------------
ELINAM TRENDS which henceforth herein may be referred to interchangeably as "ELINAM, ELINAM TRENDZ, Us, We, Our", is an e-commerce platform which aims to facilitate the ease of trade between buyers and suppliers or manufacturers, by creating that unique link connecting the buyers and the suppliers or manufacturers base at large.
ELINAM in its quest to be truly different, provides our customers with what could be described as "not your regular shopping experience" which manifests in our
       * Products Categorizing
       * Pricing
       * Shopping and Delivery
       * Unique 24/7 Customer Service
Just to mention a few. In our bid to also harness the collective effort to push the "MADE IN GHANA AGENDA", we severally list out our credible and trustworthy Ghanaian partner manufacturers and brands, a move that aims to give our customers a sense about the Ghana brands which hitherto may be unknown and unappreciated.
At ELINAM, we also pride ourselves in the superb customer service experience we provide our customers, always trying to improve upon it time and again, get in touch with us through any of our customer support platforms, and experience our world of superb customer service. Have any doubts, questions, suggestions, criticism, opinion, motivation or maybe just a simple appreciation response or feedback, we will be glad to have receipt of them in our mails and we will address all appropriately.
Moreover, ELINAM wishes to state quite vehemently that, we do not manufacture or produce any of the products offered on our platform. Any manufacture or product defects thereof in any product shall be dealt with according to our
THIRD PARTY POLICY
--------------------------------------------------------------
We also wish to state that we will make sure that third party or user policies from our partner manufactures and suppliers will be followed to the later and within their legal stipulation.
Moreso, we also wish to state that product pictures uploaded on our platform unless otherwise stated belong to our third party service providers. While ELINAM may modify in no harmful way any of the pictures, however upon the request or approach of our third party service providers to take them off our platform, we will oblige.
Our services may be interrupted, due to maintenance work or upgrade of our platform, or which could also be caused by network or equipment failure. Please also note that our services may also be disrupted by events beyond our control such as court orders, wars and natural disasters.
In any such situations stated above, ELINAM wishes to state that neither we nor any of our third party service providers will be held liable to any loss encountered by a user on the platform, we will try or best to help customers based on humanitarian grounds, however we will not be held liable legally.


TERMS OF USE
--------------------------------------------------------------
1. DOWNLOAD AND ACCOUNT SETUP
In order to use the services of ELINAM, you must download our app from the google play store and proceed to setup your account upon download. Please you must endeavor to provide us with accurate information when setting up your account, as this will help us better our service provision to you and also help us get your personalized services.
Users must have the right to claim ownership of information provided during account set up and also the right to grant ELINAM the right to use the information provided. You are solely responsible for keeping your ELINAM Account safe on any platform you access it from, but you must endeavor to get in touch with us rather promptly in case or suspect of any unauthorized use or attempted use or any other security breach of your account.
You also agree to receive text messages and sometimes also phone calls from us in future updates of ELINAM during account set up.
2. AGE RESTRICTION
 ELINAM users must be at least 16 years old to enjoy the services of our app without any parental control or approval. Users must also be able to earn income on their own and have such ability or freedom of solely deciding how to use or spend ones earning or income.
In any instance where an ELINAM user goes contrarily of the aforementioned term of use, ELINAM wishes to state emphatically that we will not be held liable or responsible to any legal issues thereof
3. THIRD PARTY POLICY
The services we provide you allows you access to use and interact with third party services and products. Please note that inasmuch as we engage third party services and parties within their legal framework, their products and services are covered by their own terms and conditions.
4. INAPPROPRIATE USE
We wish to make it known to our customer base that ELINAM must and should be used for its intended purpose only, which is e-commerce and within our terms and conditions. Inappropriate or fraudulent use of ELINAM and or our products and services shall be dealt with according to law.
Users must access (download and account setup) and enjoy our services within the confinement of the of the law and our terms of use and also only for ELINAM’s intended purpose. Users will not use our services or help others use our services in disregard of all terms mentioned herein or in ways that may hurt us or other users such us publicity, privacy, intellectual property and other online rights infringement.
You must also not use ELINAM in ways that are obscene, derogatory, threatful, defamatory, intimidating, harassing or ethnically, religiously and racially offensive. Moreso you must also note that ELINAM will not be held liable for any legal, health or moral implications generated from the inappropriate or abusive use of ELINAM or products and services of ELINAM.
5. LICENSE GRANT
We hereby permit you to use all our services by granting you this license subject to all our terms mentioned herein, and legally binding and enforceable by law if breached . This license granted you is however not transferable, limited and also revocable if need be and has only been granted you for - sole purpose of enabling you access our services in accordance to all aforementioned terms herein.
We may also in future, ask you to agree to additional terms for all or some of our services whenever necessary, however prior notice will be given.


PRODUCT CATEGORIZING
--------------------------------------------------------------
One of our unique features that helps us provide you with the "not your regular shopping experience" is our product categorizing or how products of a particular feature are collated under a category , to give users that unique experience. Beneath is a unique and enhanced description of some of our product categories.
1. CARE CAR
Adorn your beauty, love car. Whether you own a car or you want to gift someone who own a car a vehicle accessory, car care category got you covered. Here you can find products that improve upon the look and appearance of your car, both interior and exterior. Our several types of products and our accessories listed here will make you rethink your decision of dumping your old car where as you can get all you can to transform your old vehicle to a more beautiful one.
We have accessories for different types of cars and different brands too. One unique feature of products under this category is that the products are more of general types which could be used on different car types without necessarily specifying. All our products, just as the ones listed here are of five qualities. However, notwithstanding we will be glad to have your feedback on products form here and we will address them appropriately.
2. MADE IN GHANA
God bless our homeland Ghana. One problem a lot of Ghanaians have is how to identify and where to  purchase products made in Ghana which has always been talked about. As part of the collective efforts being made by Government and individuals as well to promote the "made in Ghana" agenda, we also in our bid to support the move has dedicated a whole category on our platform to credible and trustworthy Ghanaian brands and manufacturers.
By so doing, we hope to make users more aware of the efforts being made by our Ghanaian Manufacturers . Another unique feature of our support for the "made in Ghana Agenda" is the allocation of digital stores on our platform for each listed partner Ghanaian manufacturer or brand.
3. Manufactures AND WHOLESALERS
Under this category is a digital store of almost all manufacturing companies in Ghana. In our quest to provide our users and customers with that unique link between them and the manufacturing and suppliers base at large, we decided to create this category where customers can be able to purchase items directly from manufacturers and wholesalers at discount prices, however items purchased from here will be made on a minimum order quantity(MOQ) as stated by each manufacturer listed on our store. we on our part will rather charge customers a small fraction of the total amount of goods purchased that will enable has handle the other  processes of getting the goods from the manufacturers to our warehouse, for subsequent shipping and delivery to customers specified address
 4. SLIGHTLY USED PRODUCTS
With the slightly used products categorizing, we make available to our customers products that have been slightly used but rather still  in good shape to used again.Such products popularly known as “second-hand or home used” products can be found under this category with competitive pricing from different suppliers, which allows a user to select from among different suppliers , one with lower pricing for same product.
5.AVAILABLE NOW
Characteristic of the available now category is that, this is where you find product which are on sale now. There you may find products of other categories appearing here, that is to say a mixture of all products that happen to be readily available for your purchase.